<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Personal on Lagging Indicators</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/categories/personal/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Personal on Lagging Indicators</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.142.0</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/categories/personal/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>2 years of notes from building an app I didn&#39;t release</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2-years-of-notes-from-building-an-app-i-didnt-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2-years-of-notes-from-building-an-app-i-didnt-release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Close to 2 years ago, I had an idea for a mobile application that allowed users to store, submit, and manage tax reimbursements in foreign countries. For 2 years ago, I on and off worked on this idea and had a functioning version on my phone - and for nearly all that time, I never felt like the application was ready to release to potential users - and it doesn&amp;rsquo;t look like I&amp;rsquo;ll ever get it there.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Play 8 Red Squares</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/play-8-red-squares/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/play-8-red-squares/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I re-deployed &lt;a href=&#34;https://leppekja.github.io/8redsquares/&#34;&gt;8 Red Squares&lt;/a&gt;, a site that allows you to play through the &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Eight_queens_puzzle&#34;&gt;8 Queens Puzzle&lt;/a&gt; on different sized boards.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;https://laggingindicators.blog/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/image-5.png?w=644&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Future enhancements I&amp;rsquo;d like to add are&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Timer (for each segment), and total running time until the users solves n=8.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Better mobile support (board size 9 and 10 don&amp;rsquo;t handle small screens well).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Foundational solutions checklist, e.g., if a user wants to find all possible arrangements (excluding symmetries and rotations).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why (not) write online?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/why-not-write-online/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/why-not-write-online/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;a) improve communication skills by forcing myself to formalize an opinion. Feedback from anonymous readers may either point out an error I made while translating what I think to a written document or a flaw in the argument itself. Of course, I need to be willing to be wrong, and reminding myself that I am excited about learning is an powerful way to cope with finding errors in my work. Writing online is a low-barrier opportunity to become comfortable with this.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My UChicago MSCAPP Application Essay Answers (2018)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/my-uchicago-mscapp-application-essay-answers-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/my-uchicago-mscapp-application-essay-answers-2018/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;These were my answers to the application essay questions for &lt;a href=&#34;https://capp.uchicago.edu/&#34;&gt;UChicago&amp;rsquo;s MSCAPP program&lt;/a&gt; back from the 2018 round. Only piece of advice - make sure you know what skills or knowledge you want to get out of any MS program - which means work for a bit prior to attending.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Why is a combined program between policy and computer science a good match for your career goals? (max 300 words)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With a M.S. in Computational Analysis and Public Policy, I can support the shift from Michigan nonprofits solely serving constituents to leading communities. My primary career goal is to increase volunteerism through developing the technical expertise of the nonprofit sector. By applying data science techniques, I will provide organizations with evidence of successful interventions and expand their capacity to deliver services. To accomplish this, I need intensive direction to develop my quantitative analysis skills through computer science and statistics courses.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
