<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Windows on Lagging Indicators</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/windows/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Windows on Lagging Indicators</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.142.0</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/windows/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Viva Insights - How are you feeling?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/viva-insights-how-are-you-feeling/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/viva-insights-how-are-you-feeling/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Microsoft Teams provides an integration with Microsoft Viva, which schedules daily check-ins to record your perception of your mental state. Once a day, at 4pm, I get a notification that asks me to select one of five emojis that reflects how I feel.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;https://laggingindicators.blog/wp-content/uploads/2024/02/image-12.png?w=936&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Clearly, the last few weeks have not been particularly excellent, but I&amp;rsquo;m not sure what the value of this type of check-in or chart provides. We can come up with reasonable estimates of our own satisfaction with our work. I frequently journal, and I believe that the self-reflection forced through written inquiries gives way to a better sense of being, rather than an even shorter point-in-time indicator with almost no ambiguity.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using Observable Framework on Windows WSL and quickly deploying to GitHub Pages</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/using-observable-framework-on-windows-wsl-and-quickly-deploying-to-github-pages/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/using-observable-framework-on-windows-wsl-and-quickly-deploying-to-github-pages/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;ve got &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/observablehq/framework&#34;&gt;the framework&lt;/a&gt; installed, and just want to deploy the static pages, &lt;a href=&#34;#deploying&#34;&gt;skip to below&lt;/a&gt;. Note - my first time doing this, but it works. You can always deploy directly to Observable.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Observable Framework is &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/observablehq/framework/issues/90&#34;&gt;not supported on Windows&lt;/a&gt;, according to an issue in their GitHub. (Update Mar 2024: Observable Framework is now supported on Windows). To use it, you need to use WSL.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you want to use it through WSL, then the following still applies. Fortunately, it is very easy to do. Steps I had to take to do this:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
