<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Accessibility on Lagging Indicators</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/categories/accessibility/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Accessibility on Lagging Indicators</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.142.0</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/categories/accessibility/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>From a Mouse to a Trackball</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/from-a-mouse-to-a-trackball/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/from-a-mouse-to-a-trackball/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I recently bought the Kensington Slimblade Trackball to replace the Logitech MX Master mouse that I have been using for the last year. This is the first time that I&amp;rsquo;ve used a trackball. A couple of thoughts worth noting that are either omitted from or in conflict with other reviews:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The device is too large for me. It takes up almost an entire mousepad, and it is wide enough to force frequent movement between the trackball and the keyboard (I use a Glove80). I blame this partially on the desk, as it requires a roll-out keyboard holder that was not made to accommodate the split keyboard and the trackball. But for a trackball with &amp;ldquo;Slim&amp;rdquo; in the name, I expected it to be smaller.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Replacing a mouse with a pen and tablet?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/replacing-a-mouse-with-a-pen-and-tablet/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/replacing-a-mouse-with-a-pen-and-tablet/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;These are some thoughts about using a &lt;a href=&#34;https://estore.wacom.com/en-us/wacom-intuos-s-bluetooth-black-us-ctl4100wlk0.html&#34;&gt;Wacom Intuos Wireless Pen and Tablet&lt;/a&gt; to complement a mouse and keyboard over the past few weeks. I made this purchase in an effort to decrease forearm and finger pain from overuse working at a desk. Previously, I&amp;rsquo;ve been using the Logitech MX Master 3 For Business mouse, and I was hoping that switching to a pen and tablet would limit some of the forearm rotation that was causing me pain. While I put the mouse to the side, I am still using a Glove80 keyboard, as well as Windows Voice Access.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Glove80 Keyboard Review (3 months)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/gove80-keyboard-review-3-months/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/gove80-keyboard-review-3-months/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Some people are very into keyboards. They build them, they buy many of them, they review them. They know a lot about the software and hardware, and can describe the pros and cons of each component. When they look for a keyboard, they can use their prior experience to decide what features they care about, and can identify potential issues.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am not one of these people. But given recent wrist and forearm pain, I decided to switch impulsively to a split keyboard. I did some not-comprehensive-at-all research - I didn&amp;rsquo;t really know what I was looking at, or how to compare different brands, or what attributes to consider that would be right for me. I ended up buying the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.moergo.com/&#34;&gt;MoErgo Glove80 Split Wireless Keyboard&lt;/a&gt;, largely because the curved design, tenting system, and my perception of the company as a start-up that had a large passionate community behind the product. It also looked reasonably professional, minimal, and like it would fit on my desk.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I&#39;ll be back babe no baby</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/ill-be-back-babe-no-baby/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/ill-be-back-babe-no-baby/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In the past six months I&amp;rsquo;ve started to have finger, wrist, and forearm pain. I previously was using the Logitech Mx Mouse and keyboard for business. But due to the pronation of my wrists I wasn&amp;rsquo;t able to type at all without experience severe pain that would continue through the evening. so recently I&amp;rsquo;ve been using the Windows voice axis. To try and perform as much typing and as many actions on the computer as I can. This post Is entirely written using my voice. And as you can I sit I&amp;rsquo;m still having trouble making this a usable tool.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
