<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>News on Lagging Indicators</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/news/</link>
    <description>Recent content in News on Lagging Indicators</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.142.0</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/news/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Questions on “How Congress Can Fix Food Stamps”</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/questions-on-how-congress-can-fix-food-stamps/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/questions-on-how-congress-can-fix-food-stamps/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.nationalreview.com/&#34;&gt;National Review&lt;/a&gt; in July published a short opinion piece in July ‘24 entitled &lt;a href=&#34;https://archive.ph/RcWdh&#34;&gt;How Congress Can Fix Food Stamps&lt;/a&gt;. Sam Adolphsen, the author, argues that the cost of SNAP benefits is too high. He comments that &amp;ldquo;about 17.6 million food-stamp recipients are able-bodied adults, and about two-thirds don&amp;rsquo;t work,&amp;rdquo; which leads him to list a series of Republican-led, state-level policies that require SNAP recipients to participate in job training or employment programs. These policy decisions, Adolphsen argues throughout the article, are &amp;ldquo;common-sense&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;wildly popular among voters&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;turning a handout into the hand up that [SNAP benefits were] always supposed to be,&amp;rdquo; and are &amp;ldquo;protecting taxpayers while promoting work over welfare&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>April SNAP Updates</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/april-snap-updates/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/april-snap-updates/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Note a slightly different format to topic, rather than state-based.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;snap-interview-waivers-in-some-places-expiring&#34;&gt;Snap Interview Waivers in some places expiring&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.mdhs.ms.gov/post/expiration-of-waiver-of-interview-requirements-for-snap-benefits-in-mississippi/&#34;&gt;Expiration of Waiver of Interview Requirements for SNAP Benefits in Mississippi&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://news.yahoo.com/beltrami-county-snap-interview-waiver-023600199.html&#34;&gt;Beltrami County SNAP interview waiver ends April 30&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I would be very curious to see any study performed exploring differences in program administration and case outcomes between while the waiver was in effect, and the before / after where the waiver is not in place. How has the speed of applications changed? Overpayment or underpayment rates? What do the caseworkers think about this change? I also came across &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.reddit.com/r/foodstamps/comments/198kzdi/petitioning_for_the_end_of_snap_interview/?rdt=33738&#34;&gt;this Reddit thread on the impact of interview waivers&lt;/a&gt;, but would like to see a structured case study.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Questions on &#34;Why We Should Rethink the SNAP Interview Requirement: A Former Caseworker’s Perspective&#34;</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/a-response-to-why-we-should-rethink-the-snap-interview-requirement-a-former-caseworkers-perspective/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/a-response-to-why-we-should-rethink-the-snap-interview-requirement-a-former-caseworkers-perspective/</guid>
      <description>&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Context&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Student and supporting organizations wrote a &lt;a href=&#34;https://defendstudents.org/news/body/Student-Defense-Congressional-letter-on-SNAP-petition-FINAL.pdf&#34;&gt;letter to the USDA recommending that the SNAP application interview requirement be removed&lt;/a&gt;, with &lt;a href=&#34;https://defendstudents.org/news/student-advocacy-coalition-continues-push-for-u-s-department-of-agriculture-to-remove-barriers-to-snap-benefits&#34;&gt;the accompanying press release here&lt;/a&gt;. A news article that summarizes the entire P.R. push for this is &lt;a href=&#34;https://fortune.com/2024/01/16/food-stamps-snap-interview-obstacle/&#34;&gt;accessible here through Fortune magazine&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.clasp.org/blog/why-we-should-rethink-the-snap-interview-requirement-a-former-caseworkers-perspective/&#34;&gt;Why We Should Rethink the SNAP Interview Requirement: A Former Caseworker’s Perspective&lt;/a&gt; is an op-ed from The Center for Law and Social Policy (CLASP) which argues SNAP interviews should be made optional. Based on the author&amp;rsquo;s experience as a caseworker, the mandatory interviews are largely a pretense for detecting fraud, and the time could be better spent providing holistic assistance to SNAP participants. These &amp;ldquo;unnecessary interviews that are ineffective at finding what infinitesimal fraud exists&amp;rdquo; only serve to increase the stigma associated with accessing food stamps by treating applicants as if they &amp;ldquo;are thieves that must be watched&amp;rdquo;.&lt;a href=&#34;#9e749f2e-5a57-454a-a61c-2fdc32647381&#34;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNAP Benefits News - March 2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/snap-benefits-news-march-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/snap-benefits-news-march-2024/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Summary:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;many warnings about EBT payment scams and theft, alongside a proposal to improve security&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;state bills (and national) continue to propose work requirements and refuse additional SNAP funding for the summer&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;upcoming Farm Bill renewal is stalled by SNAP discussions and funding&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;national&#34;&gt;National&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.congress.gov/bill/118th-congress/senate-bill/1062?s=1&amp;amp;r=96&#34;&gt;Jobs and Opportunities for SNAP Act of 2023&lt;/a&gt; proposed by Senator John Kennedy in the U.S. Senate. The companion U.S. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.congress.gov/bill/118th-congress/house-bill/1550&#34;&gt;House bill is here&lt;/a&gt;. The following is copied from the summary:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNAP Benefits News - Feb 2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/snap-benefits-news-feb-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/snap-benefits-news-feb-2024/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The following is a curated list of news articles by U.S. state and nationally that discussed SNAP benefits in February 2024.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;national&#34;&gt;National&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.fns.usda.gov/snap/governor-letter-performance-operations&#34;&gt;Letter from Secretary Vilsack to Governors on SNAP Performance and Operations&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Poor performance on the SNAP efficiency measures meant 44 states got letters from the USDA expecting improvements.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.thefencepost.com/news/congressional-leaders-agree-on-ag-funding-as-vilsack-talks-about-snap-pilot/&#34;&gt;Congressional leaders agree on ag funding as Vilsack talks about SNAP pilot&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The SNAP pilot they discuss is the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.politico.com/live-updates/2024/02/16/congress/nearing-nutrition-funding-deal-spending-talks-00141962&#34;&gt;SNAP-choice pilot&lt;/a&gt;, limiting purchasable foods to “nutrient-dense” foods. Unsurprising that a paternalistic policy with the name “SNAP-choice” is being pushed by a Republican. See the next article for the industry’s response.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
