<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Links on Lagging Indicators</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/categories/links/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Links on Lagging Indicators</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.142.0</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/categories/links/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>SNAP Benefits News - Feb 2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/snap-benefits-news-feb-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/snap-benefits-news-feb-2024/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The following is a curated list of news articles by U.S. state and nationally that discussed SNAP benefits in February 2024.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;national&#34;&gt;National&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.fns.usda.gov/snap/governor-letter-performance-operations&#34;&gt;Letter from Secretary Vilsack to Governors on SNAP Performance and Operations&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Poor performance on the SNAP efficiency measures meant 44 states got letters from the USDA expecting improvements.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.thefencepost.com/news/congressional-leaders-agree-on-ag-funding-as-vilsack-talks-about-snap-pilot/&#34;&gt;Congressional leaders agree on ag funding as Vilsack talks about SNAP pilot&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The SNAP pilot they discuss is the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.politico.com/live-updates/2024/02/16/congress/nearing-nutrition-funding-deal-spending-talks-00141962&#34;&gt;SNAP-choice pilot&lt;/a&gt;, limiting purchasable foods to “nutrient-dense” foods. Unsurprising that a paternalistic policy with the name “SNAP-choice” is being pushed by a Republican. See the next article for the industry’s response.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monday links</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/monday-links/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/monday-links/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;- Whenever I do analyses I am nervous about being wrong, but using Excel&amp;rsquo;s &lt;a href=&#34;https://retractionwatch.com/2024/02/05/no-data-no-problem-undisclosed-tinkering-in-excel-behind-economics-paper/&#34;&gt;autofill function to impute data&lt;/a&gt; would have definitely been on my &amp;ldquo;this is not correct to do,&amp;rdquo; at the very least.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- Nice &lt;a href=&#34;https://mewo2.com/notes/terrain/&#34;&gt;example of a personal project&lt;/a&gt;. Contained, clear output, and interesting to the person doing it + delightful to play with and generate maps as a person who has no use for it. It&amp;rsquo;s fun!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- Helpful and clear description of how XSS (&lt;a href=&#34;https://journal.hexmos.com/domxss/&#34;&gt;cross site scripting&lt;/a&gt;) vulnerabilities work and can be identified.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Friday Links</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/friday-links/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/friday-links/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;- A series of YouTube videos on how &amp;ldquo;practical effects&amp;rdquo; in movies are highlighted by directors, actors, and viewers, but actually are building blocks to extremely realistic computer generated visual effects. I didn&amp;rsquo;t even realize much of what he showed was technically possible: it makes sense that performing a stunt in real life can give VFX artists valuable information about how it should look when it is computer generated, but the fact that oftentimes the stunt itself is replaced with CGI is astounding; see, for instance, the Top Gun: Maverick replacement jets.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
