<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Snap on Lagging Indicators</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/snap/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Snap on Lagging Indicators</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.142.0</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/snap/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Questions on “How Congress Can Fix Food Stamps”</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/questions-on-how-congress-can-fix-food-stamps/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/questions-on-how-congress-can-fix-food-stamps/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.nationalreview.com/&#34;&gt;National Review&lt;/a&gt; in July published a short opinion piece in July ‘24 entitled &lt;a href=&#34;https://archive.ph/RcWdh&#34;&gt;How Congress Can Fix Food Stamps&lt;/a&gt;. Sam Adolphsen, the author, argues that the cost of SNAP benefits is too high. He comments that &amp;ldquo;about 17.6 million food-stamp recipients are able-bodied adults, and about two-thirds don&amp;rsquo;t work,&amp;rdquo; which leads him to list a series of Republican-led, state-level policies that require SNAP recipients to participate in job training or employment programs. These policy decisions, Adolphsen argues throughout the article, are &amp;ldquo;common-sense&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;wildly popular among voters&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;turning a handout into the hand up that [SNAP benefits were] always supposed to be,&amp;rdquo; and are &amp;ldquo;protecting taxpayers while promoting work over welfare&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Daily SNAP News Aggregator launched</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/daily-snap-news-aggregator-launched/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/daily-snap-news-aggregator-launched/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Site is &lt;a href=&#34;https://leppekja.github.io/snap_news/&#34;&gt;accessible here&lt;/a&gt;, and the accompanying GitHub repository can be accessed through that site as well. It is based on a Google Alerts RSS feed, built every ~6 hours with Jekyll and GitHub Actions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Monthly commentary will be included on that site in the future. Immediate next steps are to add in more news aggregators as sources, to try and get articles that are missed. I would like to integrate Google Scholar as well, but it does not appear they offer an RSS feed or any simple method. Article display filtering is currently done on a keyword basis, which has been working fine, but would like to move to a classifier model.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
