<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Living-Abroad on Lagging Indicators</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/categories/living-abroad/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Living-Abroad on Lagging Indicators</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.142.0</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/categories/living-abroad/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>All my cultural tourism is commercial exchanges</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/all-my-cultural-tourism-is-commercial-exchanges/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/all-my-cultural-tourism-is-commercial-exchanges/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I recently went on a weekend trip, where I counted each time that I interacted with a person who was a citizen of the country I was visiting. I did not include any interactions with individuals at the airport prior to landing at the destination, nor once I reached the airport to return. Non-verbal interactions were not considered, e.g., making room for someone on the sidewalk, or gesturing for a car to go first at an intersection.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thoughts on Babbel Live Classes</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/thoughts-on-babbel-live-classes/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/thoughts-on-babbel-live-classes/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I took about 70 classes over a one-year unlimited class subscription with &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.babbel.com/live&#34;&gt;Babbel Live&lt;/a&gt; for Spanish from mid-2022 to 2023. My level was beginner to low intermediate over the course of the year, and I only took classes in the A1, A2, and B1 range. Prior to the classes, I was working with &lt;a href=&#34;https://apps.ankiweb.net/&#34;&gt;Anki flashcards&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.duolingo.com/&#34;&gt;Duolingo&lt;/a&gt; lessons. What follows are some thoughts I had wrote down while taking the courses. &lt;strong&gt;Some aspects of the course may have changed since I took them.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dead Butterflies, Broken Cars</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/dead-butterflies-broken-cars/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/dead-butterflies-broken-cars/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;227 vehicles have passed by us in the last hour. We are parked on the side of the road, in a car that is leaking oil. At least the hood has stopped smoking. Our two friends left in a taxi to Taluca, the closest town, to see a mechanic and have a grua tow us either to the town, or back all the way to Mexico City.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We had gone to the park to see the monarch butterflies before they begin their migration north; we arrived too late, the mariposas had left three days prior, but the trail was still open at a discount, and many bodies of the  butterflies that died were still littered on the edges of the walking paths, the ticket takers told us. We had driven about 2 hours out of the city to see them; we were three days and two hours too late.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
