<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Reviews on Lagging Indicators</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/reviews/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Reviews on Lagging Indicators</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.142.0</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/reviews/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Replacing a mouse with a pen and tablet?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/replacing-a-mouse-with-a-pen-and-tablet/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/replacing-a-mouse-with-a-pen-and-tablet/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;These are some thoughts about using a &lt;a href=&#34;https://estore.wacom.com/en-us/wacom-intuos-s-bluetooth-black-us-ctl4100wlk0.html&#34;&gt;Wacom Intuos Wireless Pen and Tablet&lt;/a&gt; to complement a mouse and keyboard over the past few weeks. I made this purchase in an effort to decrease forearm and finger pain from overuse working at a desk. Previously, I&amp;rsquo;ve been using the Logitech MX Master 3 For Business mouse, and I was hoping that switching to a pen and tablet would limit some of the forearm rotation that was causing me pain. While I put the mouse to the side, I am still using a Glove80 keyboard, as well as Windows Voice Access.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Glove80 Keyboard Review (3 months)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/gove80-keyboard-review-3-months/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/gove80-keyboard-review-3-months/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Some people are very into keyboards. They build them, they buy many of them, they review them. They know a lot about the software and hardware, and can describe the pros and cons of each component. When they look for a keyboard, they can use their prior experience to decide what features they care about, and can identify potential issues.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am not one of these people. But given recent wrist and forearm pain, I decided to switch impulsively to a split keyboard. I did some not-comprehensive-at-all research - I didn&amp;rsquo;t really know what I was looking at, or how to compare different brands, or what attributes to consider that would be right for me. I ended up buying the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.moergo.com/&#34;&gt;MoErgo Glove80 Split Wireless Keyboard&lt;/a&gt;, largely because the curved design, tenting system, and my perception of the company as a start-up that had a large passionate community behind the product. It also looked reasonably professional, minimal, and like it would fit on my desk.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
