<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Review on Lagging Indicators</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/categories/review/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Review on Lagging Indicators</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.142.0</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/categories/review/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Questions on “How Congress Can Fix Food Stamps”</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/questions-on-how-congress-can-fix-food-stamps/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/questions-on-how-congress-can-fix-food-stamps/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.nationalreview.com/&#34;&gt;National Review&lt;/a&gt; in July published a short opinion piece in July ‘24 entitled &lt;a href=&#34;https://archive.ph/RcWdh&#34;&gt;How Congress Can Fix Food Stamps&lt;/a&gt;. Sam Adolphsen, the author, argues that the cost of SNAP benefits is too high. He comments that &amp;ldquo;about 17.6 million food-stamp recipients are able-bodied adults, and about two-thirds don&amp;rsquo;t work,&amp;rdquo; which leads him to list a series of Republican-led, state-level policies that require SNAP recipients to participate in job training or employment programs. These policy decisions, Adolphsen argues throughout the article, are &amp;ldquo;common-sense&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;wildly popular among voters&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;turning a handout into the hand up that [SNAP benefits were] always supposed to be,&amp;rdquo; and are &amp;ldquo;protecting taxpayers while promoting work over welfare&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Replacing a mouse with a pen and tablet?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/replacing-a-mouse-with-a-pen-and-tablet/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/replacing-a-mouse-with-a-pen-and-tablet/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;These are some thoughts about using a &lt;a href=&#34;https://estore.wacom.com/en-us/wacom-intuos-s-bluetooth-black-us-ctl4100wlk0.html&#34;&gt;Wacom Intuos Wireless Pen and Tablet&lt;/a&gt; to complement a mouse and keyboard over the past few weeks. I made this purchase in an effort to decrease forearm and finger pain from overuse working at a desk. Previously, I&amp;rsquo;ve been using the Logitech MX Master 3 For Business mouse, and I was hoping that switching to a pen and tablet would limit some of the forearm rotation that was causing me pain. While I put the mouse to the side, I am still using a Glove80 keyboard, as well as Windows Voice Access.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Viva Insights - How are you feeling?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/viva-insights-how-are-you-feeling/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/viva-insights-how-are-you-feeling/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Microsoft Teams provides an integration with Microsoft Viva, which schedules daily check-ins to record your perception of your mental state. Once a day, at 4pm, I get a notification that asks me to select one of five emojis that reflects how I feel.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;https://laggingindicators.blog/wp-content/uploads/2024/02/image-12.png?w=936&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Clearly, the last few weeks have not been particularly excellent, but I&amp;rsquo;m not sure what the value of this type of check-in or chart provides. We can come up with reasonable estimates of our own satisfaction with our work. I frequently journal, and I believe that the self-reflection forced through written inquiries gives way to a better sense of being, rather than an even shorter point-in-time indicator with almost no ambiguity.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thoughts on Babbel Live Classes</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/thoughts-on-babbel-live-classes/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/thoughts-on-babbel-live-classes/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I took about 70 classes over a one-year unlimited class subscription with &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.babbel.com/live&#34;&gt;Babbel Live&lt;/a&gt; for Spanish from mid-2022 to 2023. My level was beginner to low intermediate over the course of the year, and I only took classes in the A1, A2, and B1 range. Prior to the classes, I was working with &lt;a href=&#34;https://apps.ankiweb.net/&#34;&gt;Anki flashcards&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.duolingo.com/&#34;&gt;Duolingo&lt;/a&gt; lessons. What follows are some thoughts I had wrote down while taking the courses. &lt;strong&gt;Some aspects of the course may have changed since I took them.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
